好了  各位  大家听我说
Okay, everybody. Listen up.
由于现在有了新宝宝
Now that we have the new baby,
所以咱们邓肯家没办法
The Duncan's are not going to be
再继续暑假家族旅行
able to do our summer vacation.
-耶  -太棒了
-Yay! -Yes!
用我们以往的形式
Like we usually do.
总是有后半句转折  为什么总是有后半句转折
There's always more. Why is there always more?
所以  我们的计划更改为去山上玩几天
So, the plan is to head up to the mountains for a few days.
爸爸为此做了很大贡献
Dad got a great deal.
-哦  不  太可怕了  -本来挺好的事
-Oh, no. This is bad. -This should be good.
好吧  我知道我以
Okay, I know I got a reputation for
搞砸出油起居而出名
finding less than stellar accommodations.
但是这一回  一切都会很完美
But this time, it's gonna be great.
我们会住进一个美丽的乡村小屋里  就在  呃
We're gonna be staying in a beautiful, rustic cabin on, uh..
死者之湖
Dead man's lake.
你说什么
What was that?
嗯  呃
Hmm? um..
死者之湖
Dead man's lake.
你是想要说死者之湖吗
Are.. are you trying to say dead man's lake?
确切的说  我是不想把它说出口
I'm trying not to, actually.
噢  别这样  大家伙  你们一旦
Oh, come on, you guys. Once you get
接受了这个名字  那地方其实很棒的
past the name, the place is amazing
死者之湖
Dead man's lake?
怎么着  我们是要去抓些死鱼
What, are we gonna catch some dead fish,
还是要在死树之间散步
or hike through dead trees?
对啊
Yeah.
爬上一些死石头
Climb on some dead rocks.
活石头也成  随你便
Or live rocks, whatever.
现在我仔细想想  觉得这计划听起来真的很不错
Now that I think about it, that sounds really nice.
就我个人来说  我一直期待着能
And I for one, am looking forward to
和家人一起度过有意义的时光
spending some quality time with my family.
鲍伯  我们生了这么多孩子
We made a lot of kids, Bob.
终于有一个拿得出手的了
That one turned out good.
喂  艾薇  是这样  听我说
Ivy, hi. Okay, so listen up.
这周末来我家举办大型派对
Big party at my house this weekend.
我们全家都会出门  我会装病留在家里的
My family's going away and I'm going to pretend to be sick.
所以去通知大家
So get the word out that..
邓肯一家要去欢度暑假啦
The Duncan family is going on a summer vacation.
是艾薇  我正在跟她说度假旅行的事呢
It was Ivy. I was telling her about the big trip.
亲爱的  谢谢你刚才说出那番话
Honey, thank you for what you said in there.
真是太贴心了
That was very sweet.
应该的  该说还是要说的
Yeah, well, it needed to be said.
你是不是感觉不太舒服
Are you coming down with something?
没什么  只是嗓子有点痒痒的
Oh, no. It's just a little tickle.
我相信到了周末就会没事了
I'm sure I will be fine for the weekend.
欢乐家庭
Family fun!
耶
Yay!
噢  又来了
Oh. There it is again.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Enpistu
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： Johnny-Z
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第九集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E09  Baby's First Vacation
好了
Okay.
我觉得必需品已经全都准备好了
So, I think we have all the essentials.
水壶  防晒霜  驱虫剂
Water bottles, sun screen, bug repellent.
笔记本  游戏机  手柄
Laptop, hand held, game controller.
孩子们  咱们只在那呆三天
Guys. We're only going for three days.
三天
Three days?
咱得再多带点游戏
We're gonna need more games.
亲爱的  泰迪在哪里
Honey, where's Teddy?
我在这儿
Here I am.
泰迪  你生病了吗
Teddy, are you sick?
是啊  我本来是多么期待
Yes, and I was so looking forward to..
家庭聚会的欢乐时光啊
Family vacation fun time.
噢
Oh.
鲍伯  我们该怎么办  要取消旅行吗
Bob, what are we going to do? Cancel the trip?
不不不  你们尽管去吧
Oh, no, no. You guys go.
艾薇可以过来陪我的
Ivy can come and stay with me,
而且达布尼太太就在隔壁
and Mrs. Dabney's right next door.
我  我不知道
I don't.. I don't know.
再说  我也不想把病传染给宝宝
Plus, I would hate to get the baby sick.
你说得言之有理
That's a good point.
是不是啊
Isn't it?
对了  我们可以通过
Hey, we can keep an eye on her
家庭监控系统看着她
with the home monitoring system.
什  什么
With.. with the..
通过什么来着
With the what now?
上周我去给一家
Last week I did a pest control job
家庭安保公司做驱虫
for a home security company.
他们免费送了我一套系统  看
They gave me a system for free. Look.
装了个摄像头  就在那儿
Got a camera right over there.
这东西是一直都开着吗
So it's on all the time?
每时每刻
24-7.
这样一来  就算我们在山里的时候  也能
So, while we're in the mountains, we can watch the
通过观看你妈电脑上的视频  了解你的情况
feed through mom's computer, and keep an eye on you.
真棒啊
Yay.
嘿  大伙儿  集合  出发了
Hey. Guys, come on, let's go!
再见  托比
Bye-bye, Toby.
查莉  亲爱的  宝宝也要和我们一起来
Charlie, honey, the baby's coming with us.
哦  讨厌
Oh, nuts.
嘿  你这话是从哪儿学来的
Um, where did you learn to say that?
哦  亲爱的  宝贝总会长大的
Oh, honey, baby needs a change.
哦  讨厌
Oh, nuts.
就是那边那玩意儿  是不
So that's it over there, huh?
没错
Yup.
我家新的安保系统
Our new security system,
也可以称之为  派对杀手9000
also known as the party killer 9,000.
为啥是9000
Why 9,000?
加上个数字多好玩
It's funnier with a number.
有吗
Is it?
那  你爸妈能听到咱们说话吗
So, will your parents be able to hear us?
不  没有声音  他们只能看到咱们的图像
No, there's no sound. They'll just be able to see us.
那我猜咱们的派对是要取消了吧
Then I guess we gotta cancel the party.
猜错了  我有好对策
Wrong. I have a plan.
他来得还真准时
And he's right on time.
维克多  快进来
Victor. come on in.
艾薇  这是维克多
Ivy, you know Victor.
南部高中音视频协会主席
President of south high's audio visual club.
谢谢你使用我的全称
Thank you for using my full title.
我总是得不到应有的尊重
I don't always get the respect I deserve.
这就是你的对策吗
This is your plan?
废材维克多
Victor the loser?
正确发音是  废柴
It's pronounced deleseur.
维克多  我想邀请你参加今晚的派对
Victor, I wanted to invite you to a party tonight.
这么说  呃  你终于把那个笨蛋斯宾塞给甩了
So, you, uh, finally got rid of that dumb jock, Spencer?
不是的  他刚好不在镇上
No. He's just out of town.
哦  请别把我刚才说的话告诉他
Oh, please don't tell him I said that.
是这样  维克多  我们需要一些音视频方面的协助
Look, Victor. We need some audio visual help.
你懂摄像头吗
Do you know anything about cameras?
你问我懂不懂摄像头
Do I know anything about cameras?
你从何方而来
Oh mahn dore tool-ee-ell lay?
哦  对了  这是用精灵语说“你从何方而来”
Oh, well, that's Elvish for "from what land do you come"?
精灵语
Elvish?
我一激动就爱溜达出几句
I slip into it when I'm excited.
我想说的是  我了解摄像头所有的一切
What I'm trying to say is I know everything about cameras.
下回直接这样说就好
Next time, just say it like that.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你  你要去哪里
Wh.. where are you going?
去告诉我妈一声这不是个陷阱
Well, to tell my mother this wasn't a trap,
可以让她先回家了
and she may proce back home.
哇
Wow.
真有你的  老爸
I gotta hand it to you, dad.
这地方挺不赖嘛
This place is pretty nice.
哦  你先等一下
Oh. hold that thought.
阴森的肖像画
Spooky portrait.
谁会在乎一幅蠢画啊
Who cares about a stupid picture?
这里简直就是天堂
I think we can call this a win.
没错  它的视线在追随你
Yep. The eyes follow you.
好了  我觉得这里相当不错
Well, I think it's very nice.
你觉得呢  查莉
What do you think, charlie?
为什么托比也来了
Why is Toby here?
好了  你真的该放下这件事了
Okay, you really gotta let that go.
走吧  咱们去看看你的房间
Come on, let's go check out your room.
过来
Come on.
好吧  鉴于只有这幅画是
Well, as long as the picture's the
这地方唯一恐怖的东西
only spooky thing about the place.
我也觉得还不错
I think we're good.
下午好
Afternoon..
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫威拉德  是这里的管理员
Name's Willard. I'm the caretaker.
在这儿工作三十多年了
Been working here 30-odd years.
这些年来一直都很怪异
And they have been odd.
哦  好吧  我们是邓肯一家
Okay. Well, we're the Duncans.
呃
Um..
我们租下了这个地方
We're renting the place.
哦  没想到他们依然在出租这房子
Oh, surprised to hear they're
即使发生过那样的
still renting it after the
意外
Incident.
意外  什么意外
Incident? what incident?
我说得太多了
I've said too much.
你至少要告诉我们  这里发生了哪种意外吧
Could you at least tell me what kind of incident it was?
意外欢乐  意外惊喜
Happy incident, fun incident?
这个  我还是走吧
Well, I'd better be going.
等一下  等一下  先别走  呃
Wait, wait. Before you go, uh,
你知道关于这家伙的事吗
Do you know anyting about this guy?
当然知道
Sure I do.
那是伊利亚·T·戴德曼准将
That's Commodore Elijah T. Deadman.
这就是为什么把这里称为死者之湖
That's why it's called dead man's lake.
-哦  -事实上  没有任何联系
-Oh. -Actually, no relation.
好了  居住愉快
Well, enjoy your stay.
如果你们可以
If you can.
如果你们可以  你这话是什么意思
If you can? what do you mean if you can?
你看起来有些僵硬
You seem a little tense.
给
Here.
这个可能会帮上忙
This might help.
死者按摩的优惠券
A coupon for dead man's massage?
名字不好听
Unfortunate name.
但很实惠
Great value.
盖比
Gabe?
-怎么了  -别再来耍我了
-Yeah?  -Stop messing with me.
别再  我都还没有开始呢
Stop? I haven't even started.
是你把所有抽屉都打开了
You made all the drawers pop open.
我为什么要这么做
Why would I do that?
这些抽屉弄疼你什么地方了吗
Did the drawers hurt you in any way?
没有
No.
令你感到羞辱了吗
Were you humiliated?
不会
No.
你到底了不了解我的工作啊
Do you know anything about my work?
很好  这个假喷嚏打得好
Okay. Good fake sneeze.
现在看一下体温
Now check your temperature.
你发烧了  再表现得担心点啊
You've got a fever. Show me some concern!
哦
Oh!
啊
Aah!
噢
Ooh!
哇唔
Woo!
你是在发热  又没有着火
You're hot. you're not going to burst into flames.
我只是想表演得妙趣横生一点嘛
Just trying to make it more interesting.
不  我们不想让它变得妙趣横生
No. we don't want it to be interesting.
我们正在拍摄展现你生病的枯燥镜头
We're creating boring footage of you being sick.
然后我会把它插入视频里
Then I'll insert it into the video feed,
这样在咱们开派对时  你爸妈就只能看到这段录像
And that's what your parents will see while we're partying.
真是太棒了  维克多
That's pretty good, Victor.
你说什么
Excuse me?
真是太棒了  主席大人
That's pretty good, mr. president.
好了  艾薇  到你出场了
Okay, ivy. you're on.
好
Okay.
现在喝一口
Now taste it.
嗯
Mm!
嗯-嗯
Mm-mm!
你是爱喝这碗汤  而不是在和这碗汤谈恋爱
You love the soup, you're not in love with the soup.
我们的视频拍够了没有啊
Don't we have enough video?
关机
And cut.
好了  我有一个关于派对的问题
Okay. Question about the party.
在派对上到底都要做什么啊
What exactly happens at a party?
我说  你从来都没参加过派对吗
Well, haven't you ever been to one?
没
Nope.
但是影视俱乐部大会
Although, the meetings of the av
就很疯狂
club can be quit rambunctious.
有一回  盖里的妈妈还做了爆米花
One time, Gary's mother made popcorn!
泰迪  就某种意义来说  咱们该问问自己
You know T.. at some point, we have to ask ourselves..
这值得吗
Is it worth it?
查莉  你抓到了一条鱼耶
Charlie, you caught a fish!
这是爸爸的
This is daddy's.
那条是我的
That one's mine.
她搞混了
She's confused.
我才没有呢
No, I'm not.
好吧
Okay.
你现在到一边自己玩儿去吧  好吗
Why don't you run along now, okay?
那么  你在干什么呢  亲爱的
So, what you been up to, hon?
这个嘛  小托比睡得正香
Well, Toby's in the middle of a long nap,
我呢  一直在看这本小说
and I have been enjoy this novel.
气喘吁吁的永恒
Breathless Eternity?
这是讲什么的
What's that about?
一个丢了衬衫的性感男人的故事
Some hunky guy who lost his shirt.
那个  不知道泰迪怎么样了
So, how's Teddy been doing?
咱们来看看
Let's find out.
哦  可怜的小姑娘
Oh, poor girl.
看她难受的样子
She looks miserable.
耶  我觉得自己就像胜利者维克多
Yeah! I feel like Victor da winner!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
根据现有情况做出推理
Putting two and two together.
你推理多长时间了
How long you been working on it?
阴森的肖像画  会自己打开的抽屉
The spooky portrait, the drawers that open
鬼鬼祟祟的管理员
by themselves, freaky caretaker.
别笑话我  但据我分析这房子是在闹鬼
Don't laugh at me, but I think this house is haunted.
老弟  都说别笑话我了
Dude! I said don't laugh at me.
不是我
That wasn't me.
我笑话你的时候  会发出这种动静
When I laugh at you, it sounds like this.
对不对
Right?
那会是谁呢
So who was that?
我  我不知道
I.. I don't know.
大概是风声吧
Maybe it's just the wind.
没事的  嘿  我知道有什么能让你感觉好一点
All right? Hey, you know what will make you feel better?
咱们来生一堆欢欣又美好的炉火
If we build a nice, cheerful fire.
火是好东西  火能让恶灵退散
Fire's good. Fire will ward off evil spirits.
-没错  -而且我们还可以生更多
-Right. -Plus we can make s'mores.
嘿 把那张旧报纸递给我
Hey, hand me that old newspaper.
看这个
Look at this.
“本地家庭发生谋杀案”
"murders at local house".
这  这  就是这栋房子
It's.. it's.. it's this house.
这里发生过谋杀案
There were murders here.
给我
Give me that.
“本日警长有个令人毛骨悚然的发现”
"the sheriff made a gruesome discovery today"
“一对度假旅行中夫妻的尸体”
"when the bodies of a vacationing couple"
“在死者之湖的一座小木屋被找到”
"were found at a cabin on dead man's lake".
我就觉得这栋房子不对劲
I knew there was something wrong with this house.
这是座凶宅
It's a murder house.
多谢你啊  老爸
Thank you, dad.
你先冷静点
Just calm down.
仅凭这里之前曾经发生过谋杀案
Just because there was a murder here before,
并不意味着还会继续发生谋杀啊
Doesn't mean there's gonna be more.
你跟他说吧
Tell him that.
PJ  盖比
PJ, Gabe.
他知道我们的名字
It knows our names!
是老爸  杀手是老爸
It's dad! The murderer's dad!
嘿  你们俩在整什么幺蛾子
Hey, what the heck is wrong with you two?
我不过是去劈些柴火
I'm just chopping some firewood.
爸爸  这栋房子发生过谋杀案
Dad, there were murders in this house.
-你快看报纸  -报纸到哪去了
-Look at the newspaper.  -Where's the paper?
报纸消失了
The newspaper's gone!
报纸  哦  在这里
The newspaper's.. oh, there it is.
你先冷静下来好吗
Would you please calm down?
这没什么好怕的
There is nothing to be afraid of.
-晚上好  -啊
-Evening.  -Ah!
哎呀  你别再这样吓人了行吗
Jeez! You've got to stop doing that.
我只是过来看看你们是不是还在这里
Just came to check and see if you were still here.
我们为什么要离开
Why wouldn't we be?
没有原因
No reason.
那  晚安
Goodnight, now.
等一下  你知道关于这件事的情况吗
Wait. Do you know anything about this?
谋杀案
The murders?
知道啊  这是未解之谜
Yeah. They were never solved.
来这里的大多数人都认为凶手是
Most people up here think the killer was..
我说得太多了
I've said too much.
你从来就没把一句话说全过  拜托  多说点吧
You never say enough. Please, finish your sentences.
一些人认为杀手就是
Some folks think the killer is the angry spirit of..
伊利亚·T·戴德曼准将的凶灵
Commodore Elijah T. Deadman.
当然  还有些人有不同的见解
Of course other folks have a different theory.
很好  是什么呢
Okay. What's that?
认为杀手是我
That it's me.
好吧  兄弟俩就像夏奇和史酷比
Well, Shaggy and Scooby are convinced
非说这栋房子里有个杀手幽灵在闹鬼
the house is haunted by a killer ghost.
（《史酷比》里的角色和情节）
鲍伯  你来看看这个
Bob, come here. Look at this.
艾薇在给泰迪送汤
Ivy's giving Teddy soup.
怎么了
So?
怎么了  她一个小时里都送了三次汤了
So, she's given her soup three times in the last hour.
看起来像是在循环播放
It's like it's on a continuous loop.
你说是不是泰迪在耍什么花招
You think Teddy's up to something?
她可是我的女儿
She's my daughter.
我就知道她会耍花招
I know she's up to something.
当然  她也是你的女儿
Of course, she's your daughter, too,
所以她的计划总失败
so she shouldn't able to pull it off.
嘿  泰迪不接电话
Hey. Teddy's not picking up.
没关系  我有个更好的主意
You know what? I have a better idea.
喂  达布尼太太吗  我是艾米·邓肯
Hi, Mrs. Dabney, it's Amy Duncan.
不  别挂电话
No, don't hang up.
嘘  伙计们  安静
Shh! Guys.. guys.
你好  达布尼太太  有什么事吗
Hi, Mrs. Dabney. What's up?
你妈妈打电话来让我查看你的情况
Your mother called and asked me to check on you.
她说你病了
Said you were sick.
哦
Oh.
对  我的感冒真的很严重
Yeah, I've got a really bad cold.
所以你就把派对礼服穿上了是吗
So you put on a party dress?
它总能让我觉得开心点嘛
It always cheers me up.
你知道什么事能让我感到开心吗
You know what cheers me up?
就是拆穿向父母说谎的小孩
Busting kids who lie to their parents.
真的吗  这样做会让你开心吗
Really? That cheers you up?
萝卜青菜  各有所爱
We all have our things.
好吧  达布尼太太
Okay, Mrs. Dabney.
你逮到我了  你打算把我怎么样
You got me. What are you gonna do?
你走运了  有一件事情
Lucky for you, there's one thing
比拆穿谎言还要合我心意
I like more than busting kids.
-是什么  -让我参加派对
-What's that? -Getting my party on.
好吧  那么说
Okay, so..
要是我邀请你参加派对  你就能保守秘密吗
If I invite you to the party, this stays between us?
就这么定了
You got a deal.
啊  快请进
Ah, come on in.
我先去给你妈妈打电话  告诉她一切正常
Let me call your mother and tell her everything's okay.
然后就回来  哦  我有个问题
Then I'll be back. Oh, one question..
现在的小孩还跳“哈梭舞”吗
Are kids these days still doing "the hustle"?
那是什么
What's that?
哦  你一定会喜欢的
Ooh. You are in for a treat.
非常感谢你跑一趟  达布尼太太
Well, thank you very much for checking Mrs. Dabney.
我  不好意思打扰你了
I'm.. I'm sorry to have bothered you.
真奇怪  她说泰迪就
I don't get it, she said Teddy was
躺在沙发上  病入膏肓
laying on the couch sick as a dog.
那很好啊
That's nice.
嗨  妈妈
Hi, mommy.
你们有什么事吗
May we help you?
查莉有点害怕  她特别想让我们大家都过来
Charlie got scared, and thought it would be a good idea
和你们一起睡
if we all came and slept with you.
我才没有呢
No, I didn't.
她不好意思承认
She's embarrassed.
好吧  就一小会儿哦
Okay, just for a little while.
你的小膝盖为啥总能踢那么准
Why do little knees always find that spot?
哦
Oh..
这派对是不是超棒的啊
Is this a great party or what?
不  我是真的在问你
No, really. I'm asking.
我没什么标准可以作为参照
I have no frame of reference.
哎  达布尼太太呢
Hey, where's Mrs. Dabney?
我记得她不是说要过来吗
I thought she was supposed to be coming over?
她可能是找不到什么合适的衣服穿
Maybe she couldn't find something to wear.
你家唱机在哪  我已经准备好摇摆起来了
Where's your turntable? I'm ready to boogie!
好了  那是什么声音
Okay, what was that?
是幽灵
It's the ghost.
-或者是杀手  -或者是杀手的幽灵
-Or the killer. -Or the killer ghost.
或者是幽灵杀手
Or the ghost killer.
鲍伯  快醒醒
Bob, wake up.
我起来了  我起来了  起来了
I'm up! I'm up. I'm up.
鲍伯  鲍伯  把灯打开
Bob.. Bob, turn on the lights.
灯坏了
They don't work.
我有个问题
Question.
那面墙今天下午的时候就在淌红水了吗
Was that wall dripping red ooze this afternoon?
另一个问题
Follow up question,
你们还有谁能看到那个漂浮的烛台吗
Does anyone else see the floating candelabra?
滚出去
Get out!
哦
Oh!
哇啊
Whoa!
去年夏天我们遭殃
Last summer it was us.
现在轮到你们了
Now it's your turn.
他手里有把刀
He's got a knife!
你们都得死
You're all gonna die..
当你们发现自己置身“惊魂鬼屋”时
When you learn you're on "Scary House".
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
“惊魂鬼屋”  美国最具人气的真人秀节目
"Scary House".. America's favorite new reality show.
我们每期随机选出一个家庭
Where we take an average family,
让他们以为自己
and convince them
住进了一个闹鬼的房子里
in a haunted house.
这完全是个恶作剧吗
This was all a prank?
太过分了
That's terrible.
你把我们耍得像群傻子一样
You made us look like fools.
你们这些人太令人发指了
You people are disgusting.
我们家要上电视了  是不是
We're gonna be on TV, you say?
当邓肯一家预定“惊魂鬼屋”时
When the Duncans checked into "Scary House",
他们对自己的处境还全然不知
They had no idea what they were in for.
哇  妈妈  好凄厉的尖叫啊
Wow, mom. That was quite a scream.
是啊  那是PJ
Yeah, that was PJ.
如果你们想看最最恐怖的景象
And if you want to see something really scary,
请看我们在邓肯妈妈的笔记本电脑上发现了什么
Check out what we saw on mama Duncan's laptop.
那是什么
What was that?
呃
Um..
那个叫做“哈梭舞”
That is called "the hustle".
是一种在七十年代非常流行的舞蹈
It was a very popular dance move in the 1970s.
它为什么会上演在我们家客厅里
And what was it doing in our living room?
听着  妈  我没时间回答这么多问题
Look, mom. I don't have time for all these questions.
因为我得录我的视频日记了
Because I have to do my video diary.
你好  查莉  我们度过了一个充实的周末
Hi, Charlie. well, we have had quite a weekend.
可这毕竟已经成为过去了  知道吗
But you know what? It's all behind us
我们为何不把它忘记
now, so why don't we forget it.
准备迎接我们的新生活呢
And move on with our lives.
我们之中的某些人在接下来的两周里
Some of us won't be moving on with
不必准备迎接任何事情了
anything for the next two weeks.
-我吗  -没错
-Me?  -Yeah.
你喜欢吗
Can you dig it?
祝她好运吧 小查莉
Wish her good luck, Charlie.
天  你是在开玩笑吧
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
这到底还要持续多久啊
How much longer is this going to go on?
我们该怎么办
What are we going to do?
好吧  现在只有一件事可做了
Well, there's only one thing to do.
啊  非常好  拿出最佳状态来
Ah! That's it. Get your groove on.
帅呆啊  老哥
Far out, man.
我会喜欢上的
I can dig it.
-好啊  各位  -噢
-Howdy, folks.. -Oh!